Guide to the American Song Sheets Collection, circa 1830s-1920s, bulk 1850s-1880s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Confederate Pamphlets, (items 1719-1741)
  - Rally Round the Flag. (Box 5, Item 1658)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 770
  - Song. (Box 5, Item 1659)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 771
  - The Spirit of 1861 (Box 5, Item 1660)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 773
  - The Alabama Cottage. A Homely Scene. (Box 5, Item 1661)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 774
  - Jackson is Dead! (Box 5, Item 1662)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 775
  - Gen. Beauregard (Box 5, Item 1663)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 777
  - To Our Dead of New Hope (Box 5, Item 1664)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 778
  - Hurrah For Jeff. Davis. (Box 5, Item 1665)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 779
  - Kentuckians to arms!!! (Box 5, Item 1666)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 780
  - A Mother's Prayer. (Box 5, Item 1667)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 782
  - The President's Chair. (Box 5, Item 1668)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 783
  - Recognition of the Southern Confederacy. (Box 5, Item 1669)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 784
  - The Soldier and his Heart. (Box 5, Item 1670)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 785
  - The Southern Matron to her Son. (Box 5, Item 1671)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 786
  - The Southern Wagon. (Box 5, Item 1672)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 787
  - The Battle Rainbow. (Box 5, Item 1673)
    Call Number: Conf Pam # 814
  - The South. (Box 5, Item 1674)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 803
  - Battle Song of the "Black Horsemen." (Box 5, Item 1675)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 804
  - The Georgia Volunteer. (Box 5, Item 1676)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 805
  - Hurrah for Jeff. Davis (Box 5, Item 1677)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 806
  - The Confederate States. (Box 5, Item 1678)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 807
  - Dear Liberty or Maryland Will Be Free (Box 5, Item 1679)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 808
  - Rally Around the Stars and Bars (Box 5, Item 1680)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 809
  - Lines on the Death of Lieut. Gen. T.J. Jackson C.S.A. (Box 5, Item 1681)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 810
  - Stonewall Jackson's Way. (Box 5, Item 1682)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 811
  - Congratulatory Lines to Brother Jonathan, On the Dictatorship of Abe Lincoln (Box 5, Item 1683)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 812
  - The South and North. (Box 5, Item 1684)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 813
  - South Carolina, a Patriotic Ode. (Box 5, Item 1685)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 814
  - Southern Song of Liberty. (Box 5, Item 1686)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 815
  - Tennessee! Fire away! (Box 5, Item 1687)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 816
  - Texan Rangers. (Box 5, Item 1688)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 817
  - The Southern Cross. (Box 5, Item 1689)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 818
  - The Southern Men (Box 5, Item 1690)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 819
  - Maryland Zouaves Own (Box 5, Item 1691)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 840
  - John Bell of Tennessee (Box 5, Item 1692)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 841
  - The Marylander's Good Bye. (Box 5, Item 1693)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 842
  - There is Life in the Old Land Yet. (Box 5, Item 1694)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 843
  - The South. (Box 5, Item 1695)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 844
  - The Southern War Song. (Box 5, Item 1696)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 845
  - Louisiana. A Patriotic Ode. (Box 5, Item 1697)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 846
  - The Southrons Are Coming. (Box 5, Item 1698)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 847
  - Sic Semper (Box 5, Item 1699)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 848
  - General Lee. (Box 5, Item 1700)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 853
  - Gen. Scott A-Sleep. (Box 5, Item 1701)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 854
  - It is I! (Box 5, Item 1702)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 855
  - Liberty or Death (Box 5, Item 1703)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 856
  - The Bonnie Blue Flag! (Box 5, Item 1704)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 857
  - Prayer During Battle. (Box 5, Item 1705)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 860
  - Our Hope. (Box 5, Item 1706)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 861
  - Our Hope. (Box 5, Item 1707)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 862
  - Georgia, My Georgia! (Box 5, Item 1708)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 863
  - The Southern Wagon. (Box 5, Item 1709)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 864
  - Southern War Song (Box 5, Item 1710)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 865
  - A Toast to Virginia. (Box 5, Item 1711)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 866
  - A Toast to Virginia. (Box 5, Item 1712)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 867
  - The Very Latest From Butler. (Box 5, Item 1713)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 868
  - Strike for the South! (Box 5, Item 1714)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 870
  - God Be Our Trust (Box 5, Item 1715)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 871
  - Additional Words to "Maryland" (Box 5, Item 1716)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 874
  - The Battle of Manassas (Box 5, Item 1717)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 875
  - Dedicated to the Baltimore Light Artillery, CSA (Box 5, Item 1718)
    Call Number: Conf Pam 12 mo # 932
- Broadside Song Sheets, (items 1742-1769)
  Song sheets in this series are housed in the Broadsides Collection. Call numbers are listed.
  - Catherine Tehgahkwitha, The Saint of Caughnawaga (part 1) (Box 5, Item 1742)
    Call Number: Brdside Case LA1
  - Catherine Tehgahkwitha, The Saint of Caughnawaga (part 2) (Box 5, Item 1743)
  - Catherine Tehgahkwitha, The Saint of Caughnawaga (part 3) (Box 5, Item 1744)
  - Catherine Tehgahkwitha, The Saint of Caughnawaga (part 4) (Box 5, Item 1745)
  - Catherine Tehgahkwitha, The Saint of Caughnawaga (part 5) (Box 5, Item 1746)
  - Catherine Tehgahkwitha, The Saint of Caughnawaga (part 6) (Box 5, Item 1747)
  - Catherine Tehgahkwitha, The Saint of Caughnawaga (part 7) (Box 5, Item 1748)
  - Catherine Tehgahkwitha, The Saint of Caughnawaga (part 8) (Box 5, Item 1749)
  - Catherine Tehgahkwitha, The Saint of Caughnawaga (part 9) (Box 5, Item 1750)
  - Catherine Tehgahkwitha, The Saint of Caughnawaga (part 10) (Box 5, Item 1751)
  - Cleburne (Box 5, Item 1752)
    Call Number: E Pam ff#80
  - The Battle of Manassas (Box 5, Item 1753)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-58
  - Alls Well, Come to the Rescue. (Box 5, Item 1754)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-59
  - The Battle Call (Box 5, Item 1755)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-60
  - The Army of General Lee (Box 5, Item 1756)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-61
  - Virginia--A Battle Song (Box 5, Item 1757)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-62
  - Carrier's Address to the Readers of the "Arkansas Patriot" (Box 5, Item 1758)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-63
  - M'Clellan's Defeat (Box 5, Item 1759)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-69
  - Yankee Vandals (Box 5, Item 1760)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-73
  - Lines Respectfully Dedicated to the Anderson Volunteers. (Box 5, Item 1761)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-74
  - Southern Yankee Doodle (Box 5, Item 1762)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-75
  - Letter (Box 5, Item 1763)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-76
  - Southern Gamecocks (Box 5, Item 1764)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-77
  - Our Southern Land (Box 5, Item 1765)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-78
  - A Song of the Past (Box 5, Item 1766)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-79
  - This Banner (Box 5, Item 1767)
    Call Number: Conf. Broadside F-83
  - On Warrenton Railroad (Box 5, Item 1768)
    Call Number: Broadside F-405
  - The Battle of Magnolia Hills (Box 5, Item 1769)
    Call Number: Broadside D-75